All About TV Recordings
All About TV Recordings
1990-1995
32 linear ft.
Videotape recordings of the television show All About TV. Also includes a few recordings of Day at Night and Television in America.
3171503
Biographical History
All About TV, later called World:Comm, was a television series produced by television critic Steven H. Scheuer and Loomis Irish, Head of the Television and Radio Department at Brooklyn College. It ran on WNET-Channel 13 in New York City between 1992 and 1995. The series examined a sweeping range of issues relating to television and media, including violence on television, cameras in the courtroom, children's television, deregulation, political campaigns, advertising, soap opera addiction, coverage of Vietnam, and much more. Panelists and guests featured on its 200+ episodes included Dan Rather, Mike Wallace, John Kenneth Galbraith, Ed Koch, Bill Kurtis, Lewis Friedman, Robert MacNeil, and many more.
Day at Night was a public television series hosted by the late James Day, co-founder of KQED in San Francisco, president of the New York City television station WNET, and Chairman of the Advisory Board for City University Television in New York (CUNY TV). The show featured interviews with notable cultural and political figures conducted in the mid 1970's.
Scope and Contents of the Collection
The All About TV Recordings consists of approximately 330 videotape recordings of episodes of the 1990s series. Panlists and guests featured in the collection include David Webster, US Director for the BBC; Lawrence Grossman, President of PBS; economist John Kenneth Galbraith; journalist Bill Kurtis; New York mayor Ed Koch; NBC journlist Linda Ellerbee; journalist Daniel Schorr; television critic Pat Aufderheide; and many more. Topics addressed spanned the entire range of political, social, economic, educational and technological issues surrounding television, including social responsibility and TV, soap opera addiction, politics and television news, sex and violence, the First Amendment, television in the courtroom, children's television, Vietnam and other war coverage, the impact of media on social behavior, and much much more.
Also included in the collection are ten videorecordings of episodes of Day At Night. Interviewees are primarily from the entertainment field and include Ozzie Nelson, Art Linkletter, E.G. Marshall, and Tennessee Ernie Ford.
Finally, there are sixteen episodes of Television in America: First Person Singular, an interview series. Interviewees include Ed Bleier, Heywood Broun, Mike Wallace and other journalists.
Arrangement of the Collection
Recordings are subdivided by show title and within that are in order by the call number assigned to them during cataloging.
Related Material
has extensive collections relating to radio, television and film history, including the papers of Stephen Scheuer and Ed Bleier. Please refer to for a complete listing.
Subject and Genre Headings
Popular culture; Radio, television, film; Scheuer, Steven H.; All about TV (Television program); Day at night (Television program); Television in America (Television program); Popular culture -- United States.; Religion on television.; Television -- History.; Television -- Study and teaching.; Television and children.; Television and culture.; Television and history.; Television and politics.; Television in religion.; Television in education.; Television broadcasting -- United States.; Television broadcasting of news -- United States.; Television journalists -- United States.; Sound recordings.; Audiotapes.; Video recordings.; Videotapes.; Interviews.; Television broadcasters.; Television journalists.; Television producers.
Access Restrictions
The majority of our archival and manuscript collections are housed offsite and require advanced notice for retrieval. Researchers are encouraged to contact us in advance concerning the collection material they wish to access for their research.
Access to recordings requires advance notice in order to produce a use copy.
Acquisition Information
Transfer from Media Services, 2010.
Inventory
- All About TV
  - The world of TV commercials, B1000 (Box 1)
  - Public television: whose public, B1001 (Box 1)
  - TV, politics and the news, B1002 (Box 1)
  - Keeping your eye on TV, B1003 (Box 1)
  - CBS: reflections in a bloodshot eye. A talk with Robert Metz, B1004 (Box 1)
  - TV politics: equal time for whom, B1005 (Box 1)
  - TV sponsors: can they influence what the public sees, B1006 (Box 1)
  - A conversation with David Webster, U.S. Director for BBC, B1007 (Box 1)
  - A conversation with Lawrence K. Grossman, president of PBS, B1008 (Box 1)
  - CBS: the power and the profits. A conversation with David Halberstam, B1010 (Box 1)
  - The television documentary, B1011 (Box 2)
  - Soap opera addiction: is it harmful, B1012 (Box 2)
  - TV, politics and money Part II, B1013 (Box 2)
  - Sex and violence: viewer bait, B1014 (Box 2)
  - Social responsibility and TV Parts I - II, B1015 (Box 2)
  - Social responsibility and TV Parts I - II, B1016 (Box 2)
  - Assault on the media: the Nixon years, B1017 (Box 2)
  - The good guys, the bad guys and the First Amendment: a talk with Fred W. Friendly, B1018 (Box 2)
  - Cable TV: growth of an industry, B1019 (Box -)
  - Kojak & Co. Selling the audience, B1020 (Box 2)
  - Kojak & Co. Selling of ideas, B1021 (Box 2)
  - Kojak & Co. Selling ideologies for export, B1022 (Box 3)
  - The new television season, B1023 (Box 3)
  - The manipulators, B1024 (Box 3)
  - TV coverage of election night: which network won, B1025 (Box 3)
  - TV news: the movie, Network, B1026 (Box 3)
  - The view from highway one, B1027 (Box 3)
  - Tuning in on politics Part 1, B1029 (Box 3)
  - Freedom & fairness: another viewpoint, B1030 (Box 3)
  - The subject is soap opera, B1031 (Box 3)
  - Checks and balances in the media, B1032 (Box 3)
  - The golden age of television, B1033 (Box 4)
  - Kids, food & television, B1034 (Box 4)
  - Sex, violence and free speech, B1034 (Box 4)
  - Media ecology, B1036 (Box 4)
  - Local news: style or substance, B1037 (Box 4)
  - Local news: trojan horse in the newsroom, B1038 (Box 4)
  - A conversation with John Kenneth Galbraith, B1039 (Box 4)
  - A conversation with John Kenneth Galbraith, B1040 (Box 4)
  - Stage to screen: theater on TV, B1041 (Box 4)
  - Public TV: whose public, how public, B1042 (Box 4)
  - Television & the public interest, B1043 (Box 4)
  - TV as teacher: decoding the messages, B1044 (Box 5)
  - Censorship in the arts, B1045 (Box 5)
  - How the British view American TV, B1046 (Box 5)
  - Television cops and the law, B1047 (Box 5)
  - A conversation with Nicholas Johnson, B1048 (Box 5)
  - The CIA's secret army: an investigative report, B1049 (Box 5)
  - Visions: a conversation with Barbara Schultz, B1050 (Box 5)
  - DocuDrama: fact or fiction, B1051 (Box 5)
  - TV: the show and tell machine, B1052 (Box 5)
  - Funding the arts, B1053 (Box 5)
  - Clearing the air: a conversation with Daniel Schorr, B1054 (Box 6)
  - Televising Congress, B1055 (Box 6)
  - A conversation with Les Brown Part II, B1056 (Box 6)
  - TV sports: America's modern religion, B1057 (Box 6)
  - TV sports: coverage or control, B1058 (Box 6)
  - The TV family, B1059 (Box 6)
  - New electronic media, B1060 (Box 6)
  - TV: an international viewpoint, B1061 (Box 6)
  - Remote control Parts 1 - 2: TV manipulates America, B1062 (Box 6)
  - Remote control Parts 1 - 2: TV manipulates America, B1063 (Box 6)
  - TV journalism Parts I - II: how free, B1064 (Box 7)
  - TV journalism Parts I - II: how free, B1065 (Box 7)
  - Independent film, video and public TV, B1066 (Box 7)
  - The politics of public service advertising, B1067 (Box 7)
  - A conversation with Benjamin Hooks, B1068 (Box 7)
  - The business of commercial TV, B1069 (Box 7)
  - Conversation with Sylvester "Pat" Weaver, B1070 (Box 7)
  - Advertising on children's tv, B1071 (Box 7)
  - Television in the courtroom, B1072 (Box 7)
  - Television in the courtroom, B1073 (Box 7)
  - Business coverage on TV, B1074 (Box 8)
  - A question of access Part II: the independents sue the networks, B1075 (Box 8)
  - Communicating in the eighties, B1076 (Box 8)
  - A discussion about public television, B1077 (Box 8)
  - A conversation with Al Levin, B1078 (Box 8)
  - Let's make a deal, B1079 (Box 8)
  - Media Works: a CETA project, B1080 (Box 8)
  - Network television and the public interest, B1081 (Box 8)
  - TV and political campaigning Part II, B1082 (Box 8)
  - Carnegie Commission report Parts I - II: the future of public broadcasting, B1083 (Box 8)
  - Carnegie Commission report Parts I - II: the future of public broadcasting, B1084 (Box 9)
  - Carnegie Commission report Parts I - II: the future of public broadcasting, B1085 (Box 9)
  - Communications legislation for the 1980's, B1086 (Box 9)
  - Television and the public interest, B1087 (Box 9)
  - 10,000 nights of network television, B1088 (Box 9)
  - Cameras in the courtroom, B1089 (Box 9)
  - Media madness & our schools, B1090 (Box 9)
  - Meet the Baxters: America's newest TV family, B1091 (Box 9)
  - The dollars and cents of TV sports, B1092 (Box 9)
  - FCC to networks: c - on kids' shows, B1093 (Box 9)
  - It's still a long way, baby: women in media, B1094 (Box 10)
  - CIA on TV, B1095 (Box 10)
  - The networks: how they stole the show, B1096 (Box 10)
  - TV in the 70's: a review, B1097 (Box 10)
  - TV diplomacy Parts I - II, B1098 (Box 10)
  - TV diplomacy Parts I - II, B1099 (Box 10)
  - Talking back to your TV, B1100 (Box 10)
  - The Museum of Broadcasting, B1101 (Box 10)
  - Media As Big Business *, B1102 (Box 10)
  - The American Short Story *, B1103 (Box 10)
  - Ford Rowan - A Man with a Conscience *, B1104 (Box 11)
  - The Electronic Church *, B1105 (Box 11)
  - CIA on TV, B1106 (Box 11)
  - Cable Network News - Part Two *, B1107 (Box 11)
  - TV and Political Campaigns - Part One *, B1108 (Box 11)
  - TV and Political Campaigns - Part Two *, B1109 (Box 11)
  - A Conversation with William T. Henry II *, B1110 (Box 11)
  - Prime Time American (Robert Sklar) *, B1111 (Box 11)
  - Teaching Critical Viewing *, B1112 (Box 11)
  - The Best of International TV *, B1113 (Box 11)
  - TV Coverage of Campaign in '80 *, B1114 (Box 12)
  - The New Science Boom on TV *, B1115 (Box 12)
  - A conversation with Brian Winston, B1116 (Box 12)
  - The tonight Show, B1117 (Box 12)
  - Public TV: new directions, B1118 (Box 12)
  - Communications technology: new uses, B1119 (Box 12)
  - Local News *, B1120 (Box 12)
  - Image of Older People on TV *, B1121 (Box 12)
  - A Conversation with Henry Geller *, B1122 (Box 12)
  - A Conversation with Henry Geller - Part Two *, B1123 (Box 12)
  - Decola - NBC News Mag *, B1124 (Box 12)
  - Golden age of television, B1125 (Box 13)
  - Deregulation of the Networks *, B1126 (Box 13)
  - The Images of Businessmen on TV *, B1127 (Box 13)
  - Untitled *, B1128 (Box 13)
  - John Beck (Guest) *, B1129 (Box 13)
  - Lawrence Grossman (Guest) *, B1130 (Box 13)
  - Wicklein, Koughman - Part One *, B1131 (Box 13)
  - Wicklein, Koughman - Part Two *, B1132 (Box 13)
  - The Information Society - Part One *, B1133 (Box 13)
  - The Information Society - Part Two *, B1134 (Box 13)
  - Women in TV Sports *, B1135 (Box 13)
  - All About TV: TV News - A Conversation with Dave Marash *, B1136 (Box 14)
  - TV News - A Conversation with Dave Marash (Part Two) *, B1137 (Box 14)
  - Kicking the TV Habit *, B1138 (Box 14)
  - Nightline - New Directions in TV News *, B1139 (Box 14)
  - Women in Cable *, B1140 (Box 14)
  - Women in Cable (Part Two) *, B1141 (Box 14)
  - Programming for Cable *, B1142 (Box 14)
  - A Conversation with Tony Schwartz *, B1143 (Box 14)
  - Middletown - A Conversation with Peter Downs *, B1144 (Box 14)
  - Middletown - A Conversation with Peter Downs - Part Two *, B1145 (Box 14)
  - Low Power *, B1146 (Box 15)
  - Paul Klein, B1147 (Box 15)
  - Who Needs - of Network News *, B1148 (Box 15)
  - The 2nd American Revolution *, B1149 (Box 15)
  - New Directions in TV News *, B1150 (Box 15)
  - New Directions in TV News *, B1150 (Box 15)
  - A Conversation with Lewis Friedman - Part One *, B1151 (Box 15)
  - A Conversation with Lewis Friedman - Part Two *, B1152 (Box 15)
  - A Conversation with Bob Teague *, B1153 (Box 15)
  - CBS Cable: a look at cultural programming, B1154 (Box 15)
  - A Conversation with Robert MacNeil - Part One *, B1155 (Box 15)
  - A Conversation with Robert MacNeil - Part Two *, B1156 (Box 16)
  - A Conversation with Robert Mcneil (Copy) *, B1157 (Box 16)
  - Big Blue Marble *, B1158 (Box 16)
  - A Conversation with Paul Duke *, B1159 (Box 16)
  - A Conversation with Charles Collingwood *, B1160 (Box 16)
  - A Conversation with Charles Collingwood - Part Two *, B1161 (Box 16)
  - Information Revolution - Telextex and Videotex *, B1162 (Box 16)
  - Cable Health Network *, B1164 (Box 16)
  - Children's TV Parts 1 - 2, B1165 (Box 16)
  - Children's TV Parts 1 - 2, B1166 (Box 16)
  - Children's TV Part 2, B1167 (Box 16)
  - Children's TV Parts 1 - 2, B1167 (Box 17)
  - Children's TV Part 2, B1168 (Box 16)
  - Children's TV Parts 1 - 2, B1168 (Box 17)
  - A conversation with Frank Blair, B1169 (Box 17)
  - TV coverage of Central America Part 2, B1170 (Box 17)
  - TV coverage of South America, B1171 (Box 18)
  - Porn on Cable, B1172 (Box 17)
  - Money & politics, B1173 (Box 17)
  - Money & politics, B1174 (Box `)
  - CBS Nightwatch, B1175 (Box 17)
  - NBC Overnight, B1175 (Box 17)
  - American journey, B1176 (Box 17)
  - Dupont / Columbia Awards *, B1177 (Box 17)
  - Media Speak *, B1177 (Box 17)
  - Satellite News Network *, B1178 (Box 20)
  - War Peace and the News Media *, B1179 (Box 20)
  - DocuDrama (Parts One and Two) *, B1180 (Box 18)
  - Women and Techonlogy *, B1181 (Box 18)
  - Media monopoly, B1182 (Box 18)
  - Interview with Budd Schulberg, B1183 (Box 18)
  - Deregulation of cable, B1184 (Box 18)
  - Deregulation of Cable *, B1184 (Box 18)
  - Vietnam Parts 1-2, B1185 (Box 18)
  - Vietnam Parts 1-2, B1185a (Box 18)
  - The new season Part 2, B1186 (Box 18)
  - Technologies of freedom Parts 1 - 2, B1187 (Box 18)
  - Technologies of freedom Parts 1 - 2, B1188 (Box 18)
  - Inside prime time, B1189 (Box 19)
  - Bill Kurtis on assignment, B1190 (Box 19)
  - Channels of communications, B1191 (Box 19)
  - Children's TV, B1192 (Box 19)
  - To sing our own song: the Philippines, B1193 (Box 19)
  - Campaign alert, B1194 (Box 19)
  - Adult learning service on PBS, B1195 (Box 19)
  - Changing nature of foreign reporting, B1196 (Box 19)
  - Channels, B1197 (Box 19)
  - The public's right to know, B1198 (Box 19)
  - Higher education through telecommunications, B1199 (Box 20)
  - Soap operas, B1200 (Box 20)
  - The political documentary, B1201 (Box 20)
  - A conversation with Brian Winston, B1202 (Box 20)
  - A conversation with Stephen Fleischman Parts 1 - 2, B1203 (Box 20)
  - A conversation with Stephen Fleischman Parts 1 - 2, B1204 (Box 20)
  - Your children, our children, B1205 (Box 20)
  - A conversation with Ted Sorensen Part 2, B1206 (Box 20)
  - Lifetime, B1207 (Box 21)
  - Organized labor and TV, B1208 (Box 21)
  - The TV turnoff, B1209 (Box 21)
  - Where's cable headed, B1210 (Box 21)
  - Where's cable headed, B1211 (Box 21)
  - Concealed enemies, B1212 (Box 21)
  - Concealed enemies, B1213 (Box 21)
  - The uncounted enemyLibrary has: Part 2., B1214 (Box 21)
  - NBC in Lebanon Part 1 Part 2, B1215 (Box 21)
  - NBC in Lebanon Part 1 Part 2, B1216 (Box 21)
  - NBC in Lebanon Part 1 Part 2, B1217 (Box 22)
  - Cable T.V.franchises, B1219 (Box 22)
  - The uncounted enemyLibrary has: Part 2., B1219 (Box 21)
  - Television in American culture, B1220 (Box 22)
  - Comedy zone, B1221 (Box 22)
  - TV and the presidential election, B1222 (Box 22)
  - Civilization and the Jews, B1223 (Box 22)
  - Campaign '84, B1224 (Box 22)
  - Cameras in the courtroom Parts 1 - 2, B1225 (Box 22)
  - Cameras in the courtroom Parts 1 - 2, B1226 (Box 22)
  - Broadcast fairness, B1227 (Box 22)
  - 60 minutes, B1228 (Box 23)
  - A conversation with Bruce Christensen, B1229 (Box 23)
  - A conversation with Linda Ellerbee, B1230 (Box 23)
  - The crowded new world of TV, B1231 (Box 23)
  - TV coverage of the economy, B1232 (Box 23)
  - TV coverage of the economy, B1233 (Box 23)
  - TV coverage of the Ethiopian famine, B1234 (Box 23)
  - A conversation with Barbara Feldon, B1235 (Box 23)
  - A conversation with Ed Koch, B1236 (Box 23)
  - Dupont Columbia awards, B1237 (Box 24)
  - Beer and wine ban, B1238 (Box 24)
  - C-SPAN, B1238 (Box 24)
  - Children's programming, B1239 (Box 24)
  - A conversation with Charles Osgood, B1240 (Box 24)
  - Independent stations, B1240 (Box 24)
  - Roundup prime time, B1241 (Box 24)
  - Roundup prime time, B1242 (Box 24)
  - Crisis in Central America, B1243 (Box 24)
  - TV coverage of Central America, B1243 (Box 24)
  - Crisis in Central America, B1244 (Box 24)
  - TV coverage of Central America, B1245 (Box 24)
  - Children's TV: promise and practice, B1246 (Box 24)
  - Children's TV: promise and practice, B1247 (Box 24)
  - Vietnam Parts 1 - 2: the controversy continues, B1247 (Box 24)
  - Vietnam Parts 1 - 2: the controversy continues, B1248 (Box 25)
  - A look at CBS Part 1, B1249 (Box 25)
  - A conversation with Danial Schorr, B1250 (Box 25)
  - A Conversation with Will A. Newharth *, B1251 (Box 25)
  - The heart of the dragon, B1252 (Box 25)
  - Independent documentaries, B1253 (Box 25)
  - Nanzi Adzima Parts 1 - 2, B1254 (Box 25)
  - Nanzi Adzima Parts 1 - 2, B1255 (Box 25)
  - Television and aging, B1256 (Box 25)
  - Educational programs for children, B1257 (Box 25)
  - Public access, B1258 (Box 26)
  - CNN, B1259 (Box 26)
  - A conversation with James Duffy, B1260 (Box 26)
  - News at any cost, B1261 (Box 26)
  - Show 103 - Schechner, B1262 (Box 26)
  - The impact of media on social behavior Parts 1 - 2, B1263 (Box 26)
  - The impact of media on social behavior Parts 1 - 2, B1264 (Box 26)
  - 60 minutes, B1265 (Box 26)
  - A conversation with Mark Goodson, B1266 (Box 26)
  - West 57th, B1267 (Box 26)
  - A conversation with Richard Hottelet Parts 1-2, B1268 (Box 27)
  - A conversation with Richard Hottelet Parts 1-2, B1269 (Box 27)
  - Cablevisions, B1270 (Box 27)
  - American playhouse 5th season, B1271 (Box 27)
  - Video 1995, B1272 (Box 27)
  - Local news Part 1-2, B1273/B1274 (Box 27)
  - Children & TV, B1275 (Box 27)
  - Saturday night a backstage history of Saturday night live, B1276 (Box 27)
  - Perry Wolff, B1277 (Box 27)
  - Public access, B1278 (Box 28)
  - Financial news on TV, B1279 (Box 28)
  - Media reform, B1280 (Box 28)
  - Communicating on TV, B1281 (Box 28)
  - Funding public TV, B1282 (Box 28)
  - Documentary filmmakers, B1283 (Box 28)
  - Documentary filmmakers, B1284 (Box 28)
  - Stephen Hess, B1285 (Box 28)
  - Helen Wagner/Julianne Moore, B1286 (Box 28)
  - Kim Zimmer/Kathryn Hays, B1287 (Box 28)
  - Downsizing, B1288 (Box 29)
  - TV news, B1288 (Box 29)
  - TV news, B1289 (Box 29)
  - A conversation with Jack Willis, B1290 (Box 29)
  - Murrow Parts 1-2: his life and times, B1291 (Box 29)
  - Murrow Parts 1-2: his life and times, B1292 (Box 29)
  - The new season Parts 1-2, B1293 (Box 29)
  - Media watching, B1294 (Box 29)
  - The entrepreneurs: an American adventure, B1295 (Box 29)
  - The entrepreneurs: an American adventure, B1296 (Box 29)
  - The future of network news, B1297 (Box 29)
  - TV coverage of terrorism, B1298 (Box 30)
  - So you want to write a soap opera, B1299 (Box 30)
  - Is late night becoming prime time, B1300 (Box 30)
  - TV and the political process, B1301 (Box 30)
  - John Hendricks, B1302 (Box 30)
  - R.E. Mulholland, B1302 (Box 30)
  - David Marc and Daniel Czitrom, B1303 (Box 30)
  - Charlie Rose, B1304 (Box 30)
  - Henry Hampton: eyes on the prize, B1305 (Box 30)
  - Michael Pertschuk, B1306 (Box 30)
  - John Hess, Roger Rosenblatt, B1307 (Box 30)
  - Norman Isaacs, B1308 (Box 31)
  - James Monaco on Baseline, B1309 (Box 31)
  - Media bias, B1310 (Box 31)
  - Television, B1311 (Box 31)
  - Cable programming, B1312 (Box 31)
  - Prime times, bad times, B1313 (Box 31)
  - Prime times, bad times, B1314 (Box 31)
  - Who killed CBS, B1315 (Box 31)
  - TV critic Pat Aufderheide, B1316 (Box 31)
  - MacNeil/Lehrer newshour: campaign '88, B1317 (Box 31)
  - Demo tape, B1318 (Box 31)
  - Interviews about TV on the street, B1319 (Box 32)
  - Interviews about TV on the street, B1320 (Box 32)
  - CNN, B1321 (Box 32)
- Day At Night
  - Guest - Art Linkletter * (Box 32)
  - Guest - Burt Tillstrom * (Box 32)
  - Guest - E. G. Marshall * (Box 32)
  - Guest - Howard K. Smith * (Box 32)
  - Guest - Jonathan Winter * (Box 32)
  - Guest - Newton Minow * (Box 32)
  - Guest - Ozzie Nelson * (Box 32)
  - Guest - Sam Levinson * (Box 32)
  - Guest - Studs Terkel * (Box 32)
  - Guest - Tennessee Ernie Ford * (Box 32)
- Television in America
  - First Person Singular - Andy Rooney * (Box 32)
  - First Person Singular - Bernard Birnbaum, Part One * (Box 32)
  - First Person Singular - Bernard Birnbaum, Part Two * (Box 32)
  - First Person Singular - Ed Bleier * (Box 32)
  - First Person Singular - George Dessart * (Box 32)
  - First Person Singular - Heywood Hale Broun * (Box 32)
  - First Person Singular - John Sharnik * (Box 32)
  - First Person Singular - Mike Wallace * (Box 32)
  - First Person Singular - Perry "Skee" Wolff Part One * (Box 32)
  - First Person Singular - Phillip Scheffler * (Box 32)
  - First Person Singular - Richard Hottelet * (Box 32)
  - First Person Singular - Robin Morgan * (Box 32)
  - First Person Singular - William Baker * (Box 32)
  - First Person Singular - William Sloan * (Box 32)
  - Garrick Utley Interview Part Two * (Box 32)
  - Morley Safer Interview * (Box 32)
- Audiorecordings
  - Reel tapes, various sizes, audio only. (Box 33)
    Audiorecordings are unprocessed and not accessible to researchers at this time.